Guide to the Nelson Sullivan Video Collection 1976 - 1989 MSS 357
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Videorecordings, 1976 - 1988
  - Halloween 1984, October 31, 1984 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0204)
  - Kershaw, June 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0205)
    [1] -- Kershaw, 6/28/1985 [2] -- Kershaw, 6/29/1985
  - La Dolce Micahel Musto Party at Danceteria, December 12, 1984 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0206)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Dance Teen, April 18, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0207)
  - Alexis Del Lago's Garden Party, June 21, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0208)
  - Ethyl Eichelberger's Leer at 8BC, July 27, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0209)
  - Scott Wittman and Marc Shaiman's Nude Faces of 1985 at Danceteria, May 15, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0210)
  - Kennon, Voltaire, + Kristy Rose at Pyramid during New Music Seminar, September 26, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0211)
  - Hamlette with Ethel Eichelberger (first take), September 9, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0212)
  - Miss Margie and Lise, February 24, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0213)
  - Vito’s Bridge Party for Annie Flanders, June 6, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0214)
  - Tish’s “It’s My Party, Again” at Limelight, August 21, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0215)
  - Sylvia in Woodstock, July 29, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0216)
  - Nelson's Film School Movies, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0217)
    Nelson's Film School Movies: Fire Island 1976, Inside Disco, Walk Around Manhattan, Good Motim Montage, Sunshine in NY 1972 with Douglas and Chou and Blackout takes a walk in stop motion, Ride on Subway, Picture of Nelson, Nelson Tour of Mannequins at [Gimblls] 1972, Central Park, The Piers, Gay Bedroom Scene, Things to Look At, Movements
  - Now Explosion on MTV, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0218)
  - Mahogony at Pyramid, May 3, 1984 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0219)
  - Axelrod Wedding Party, October 27, 1984 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0220)
  - La Dolce Musto Party 1984 at Danceteria (Copy) (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0221)
  - Brant Mewborn "A Love That Lasts Forever" Original and NBC Dub, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0222)
  - Sylvia Miles on Joe Franklin, July 13, 1984 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0223)
  - Downtown Divas at Limelight, April 9, 1985 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0224)
  - Nude Faces of 1985 at Danceteria, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0225)
  - Alexis Del Lago in Ape Suit, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0226)
  - Bunny Chase the Movie (Original Edit), Kill Pig, and Titles, June 26, 1985 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0227)
  - Now Explosion at Pyramid, January 25, 1985 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0228)
  - Tom Rubnitz Oremiers Made For TV at Beulahland, The Pop Tarts at Pyramid, July 28, 1985 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0229)
    Featuring: Tabboo, Hapi Phase, Ethyl, Clit.
  - Nelson’s Family in South Carolina, Feburary 1986 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0230)
    February 24, 25, 26, 1986 Featuring: Nancy, Mama, Doris, Fred, Emma, Henry, Doris + Harry, Mrs. Mobley, Nancy - [Manot Care], Billie Jo, Peek Sisters Music Video
  - Keith Haring "Into 1984" New Year's Party, December 31, 1984 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0231)
  - Mama Said, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0232)
  - Wigstock #1, August 18, 1985 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0233)
  - Bobby and Mary Kaye’s Wedding, October 11, 1986 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0234)
  - Stringfellow’s Fashion Show #1, Now Explosion at Pyramid, May 25, 1988 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0235)
    Featuring: Mandingo and RuPaul singing Bad Bad Bad
  - Neurotic Theatrical Co., November 30, 1986 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0236)
  - Snow Angel with Sylvia Miles, 1985 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0237)
  - Now Explosion at Limelight, Bunny at Pyramid, November 24, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0238)
    Original Format: Video8mm
  - Fred’s Anti Theatre at Limelight with great pies, July 13, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0239)
  - Wigstock #2 (part 3), September 1, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0240)
  - Now Explosion Central Park and Van, May 18, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0241)
  - Now Explosion TIF, Man 2 Man at The Saint, WHISPERS at Pyramid with Lady Bunny, New Music Seminar with RuPaul, July 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0242)
    [1] -- Now Explosion TIF, 7/14/1986 [2] -- Man 2 Man at The Saint, 7/15/1986 [3] -- WHISPERS at Pyramid with Lady Bunny, 7/15/1986 [4] -- New Music Seminar with RuPaul, 7/15/1988
  - Vicki’s Party, July 27, 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0243)
  - Phyllis Tarter at Williams Residence, October 20, 1988 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0244)
  - A Coupla White Chicks (raw footage), April 12, 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0245)
  - People Tree at Pyramid, October 7, 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0246)
  - Celebrity Club with Bunny, August 30, 1988 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0247)
  - People Tree at Pyramid, May 29, 1988 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0248)
  - Pyramid Celebrates new management, Pattelson’s, G. Gnt., 5th Avenue, East Village, Eddie, Perry, etc., June 4, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0249)
    [1] -- Pyramid Celebrates new management, 6/4/1986 [2] -- Pattelson’s, G. Gnt., 5th Avenue, East Village, Eddie, Perry, etc., 10/5/1986
  - Celebrity Club, August 24, 1988 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0250)
  - Pop Tarts D&D, Now Explosion show for New Music Seminar at Limelight, July 16, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0251)
  - Now Explosion Times Square to East Village (Now Explosion outside Pyramid Club), undated (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0252)
  - Anti Theatre Wedding, July 19, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0253)
  - Phyllis Tarter Phantom of the Opera, February 1, 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0254)
  - Celebrity Club, September 14, 1988 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0255)
  - Flaunt It #2, December 7, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0256)
  - Pyramid Birthday #5, Flaunt It #3, December 14, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0257)
  - Pyramid 5th Birthday (tape #2), ED, December 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0258)
    [1] -- Pyramid 5th Birthday (tape #2), 12/14/1986 [2] -- ED, 12/17/1986
  - Pop Tarts at The Saint, November 13, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0259)
  - Dial M for Model (#2) at Limelight, November 11, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0260)
  - Kennon, Dial M for Model, Clayton's Pryamid Photo session, November 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0261)
    [1] -- Kennon, 11/10/1986 [2] -- Dial M for Model, 11/10/1986 [3] -- Clayton's Pryamid Photo session, 11/11/1986
  - L. Mandenbaum’s Birthday at Madame Rosa’s, Drag Ball (part 2), 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0262)
    [1] -- L. Mandenbaum’s Birthday at Madame Rosa’s, 9/6/1986 [2] -- Drag Ball (part 2), 10/24/1986
  - Andrea Fault at Pyramid, November 15, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0263)
  - The Last Moments of 1986, December 31, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0264)
  - Phyllis Tarter Recital, June 14, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0265)
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid with Hapi Phace, Tabboo!, ML, Ethel Eichelberger, Tompkins Square Park (Kennon, Conch, Folk singer), June 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0266)
    [1] -- WHISPERS at Pyramid with Hapi Phace, Tabboo!, ML, Ethel Eichelberger, 6/14/1986 [2] -- Tompkins Square Park (Kennon, Conch, Folk singer), 6/15/1986
  - Drag Queen Olympics at Pyramid, July 9, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0267)
  - Tabboo! At Pyramid, Kill Pig, Quando, September 27, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0268)
  - Dean Johnson’s Birthday Barbecue and Show at The World, May 31, 1988 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0269)
  - Lypsinka, La Palace de Beaute, John Sex, September 25, 1988 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0270)
  - Celebrity Club with Hapi Phace, Lizette, Lurleen, September 7, 1988 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0271)
  - John Sex at Red Garter, Marlene at Pyramid, Disco Van, September 10, 1988 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0272)
  - Mrs. Sullivan and Aunt Doris in NYC, May 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0273)
    [1] -- Mrs. Sullivan and Aunt Doris in NYC, 5/26/1986 [2] -- Mrs. Sullivan and Aunt Doris in NYC, 5/27/1986
  - Limelight - Coney Island, May 27, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0274)
  - Edit for Tunnel, January 14, 1988 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0275)
  - Wigstock III (#4), Rockets & Dave, Kennon (part 1), September 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0276)
    [1] -- Wigstock III (#4), Rockets & Dave, 9/7/1987 [2] -- Kennon (part 1), 9/10/1987
  - RuPaul fr. Erll to Grand Central, DV8 Trip to Boston (part 1), April 1988 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0277)
    [1] -- RuPaul fr. Erll to Grand Central, 4/21/1988 [2] -- DV8 Trip to Boston (part 1), 4/22/1988
  - Bobby Surprise Party, Celebrity Club, September 1988 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0278)
    [1] -- Bobby surprise party, 7/18/1988 [2] -- Celebrity Club, 7/21/1988
  - Wigstock III (part 2), September 7, 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0279)
  - Nasomi/Kill Pig - Limelight, East Village, Eddie, September 23, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0280)
  - Randy Pop’s Birthday at Cafe de la Place, September 22, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0281)
  - RuPaul Limelight - Spicey, Trade, Albert, Michael Musto, Dick (part 2), September 2, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0282)
  - RuPaul Limelight (part 1), RuPaul / Sushi / Avenue A, September 20, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0283)
  - The Wizard of Oz at Pyramid, Dainty (abortion), September 17, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0284)
  - Candy Store/Quando, November 14, 1986 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0285)
  - Bobby and Mary Kaye’s Wedding, October 11, 1986 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0286)
  - Floyd’s fashions at Tunnel, Lisa E “Positive Me” (take #1), 1988 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0287)
    [1] -- Floyd’s fashions at Tunnel, 10/13/1988 [2] -- Lisa E “Positive Me” (take #1), 10/15/1988
  - Richard Metzger’s film crew at 5 Ninth Avenue, October 1, 1988 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0288)
  - Wigstock IV (part 3), August 31, 1988 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0289)
  - Limelight Drag Show, October 12, 1986 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0290)
  - World Welcomes Michael Alig, Me and BBC, Me with Pop Tarts editing BBC piece, 1989 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0291)
    [1] -- World Welcomes Michael Alig, 1/12/1989 [2] -- Me and BBC, 1/15/1989 [3] -- Me with Pop Tarts editing BBC piece, 1/22/1989
  - Karen’s Birthday, June 20, 1986 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0292)
  - Liz at Palladium, Michael Musto, May 1986 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0293)
    [1] -- Liz at Palladium, 5/24/1986 [2] -- Michael Musto, 5/25/1986
  - MIX TAPE Craig Vandenberg edit, undated (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0294)
  - Calendar Boy Contest at Rock and Roll Fag Bar, November 29, 1988 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0295)
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid with Jayne County and Wendy Wild (with Trade and Jance), October 2, 1988 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0296)
  - Bn on TV, Dick, Palladium, Beach Party, James St. James in Deli, Limelight, Albert & Liz walk to studio with for RuPaul’s Starbooty recording session, May 1986 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0297)
    [1] -- Bn on TV, Dick, Palladium, Beach Party, James St. James in Deli, Limelight, 5/24/1986 [2] -- Albert & Liz walk to studio with for RuPaul’s Starbooty recording session, 5/25/1986
  - International Chrysis at Boy Bar, Sister Dimension at Wah Wah Hut, November 17, 1988 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0298)
  - Mars - First Sunday with Trade, undated (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0299)
  - Test Tape, undated (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0300)
  - Blackout in snow, People Tree at Pyramid, 1988 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0301)
    [1] -- Blackout in snow, 1/3/1988 [2] -- People Tree at Pyramid, 1/3/1988
  - Pyramid Club Birthday # 7, December 10, 1988 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0302)
  - Phyllis Tartar & Co. St. Saeric (part 1), June 4, 1989 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0303)
  - Phyllis Tartar & Co. St. Saeric (part 2), June 4, 1989 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0304)
  - DV8 trip to Washington on bus, Judy Garlands on Parade on Christopher Street, June 1989 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0305)
    [1] -- DV8 trip to Washington on bus, 6/21/1989 [2] -- Judy Garlands on Parade on Christopher Street, 6/23/1989
  - Trip to Atlanta airport, Atlanta, Nancy February 1 & 2 1989, February 1989 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0306)
  - Big Star on Ponce de Leon February, Lennox Square, Molly’s, The American Music Show, February 1989 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0307)
    [1] -- Big Star on Ponce de Leon February, 2/8/1989 [2] -- Lennox Square, Molly’s, The American Music Show, 2/9/1989
  - San Francisco Mix #1, undated (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0308)
  - Love Ball, Susanne Bartsch at Roseland, May 10, 1989 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0309)
  - Morning at 5 Ninth Avenue, July 4th 1986 (part 2), International Chrysis with Man 2 Man at Limelight, Philly's Birthday, July 1986 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0310)
    [1] -- Morning at 5 Ninth Avenue, 7/4/1986 [2] -- July 4th 1986 (part 2), 7/4/1986 [3] -- International Chrysis with Man 2 Man at Limelight, 7/6/1986 [4] -- Philly's Birthday, 7/9/1986
  - Flaunt It Club #1 with Phoebe Legere at Limelight, November 30, 1986 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0311)
  - Dave Smith, Jasmine, Dawn Houston, Eddie, December 3, 1986 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0312)
  - The Nelson and Eddie Christmas Special, December 25, 1986 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0313)
  - Eddie, Phoebe Legere at Freddie’s, October 15, 1986 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0314)
  - Flaunt It #4, December 21, 1986 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0315)
  - Leigh Bowery,Tom Rubnitz & Charles Atlas Birthday at John Badam's Apartment, Albert Crudo Fashion Show at Red Zone, April 3, 1989 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0316)
  - San Francisco Tapes, February 6, 1987 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0317)
  - Atlanta 1987 #2 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0318)
  - Albert Crudo, Eric Conrad and Frank Owen, Passion Rip at Tunnel (Fashion Show), March 1987 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0319)
    [1] -- Albert Crudo, Eric Conrad and Frank Owen, 3/4/1987 [2] -- Passion Rip at Tunnel (Fashion Show), 3/12/1987
  - Copy of Pyramid, Kennon at Pyramid, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0320)
    [1] -- Copy of Pyramid, 9/26/1986 [2] -- Kennon at Pyramid, 2/24/1987
  - Celebrity Club at The World, March 9, 1989 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0321)
  - S. Freedman at The World, Michael Alig Christmas, Bunny Christmas, December 1988 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0322)
    [1] -- S. Freedman at The World, 12/23/1988 [2] -- Michael Alig Christmas, 12/24/1988 [3] -- Bunny Christmas, 12/24/1988
  - Apple Love at Mars, May 28, 1989 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0323)
  - La Palace de Beaute (part 1), October 10, 1987 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0324)
  - Freddy & Michael Musto at The World, Bunny at Boy Bar, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0325)
  - Kenny at The World - Fag Bar, Michelangelo Signorelli and Michael Musto, Christina at The Tunnel, December 1987 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0326)
    [1] -- Kenny at The World - Fag Bar, 12/1/1987 [2] -- Michelangelo Signorelli and Michael Musto, 12/9/1987 [3] -- Christina at The Tunnel, 12/25/1987
  - Atlanta 1988, Monday, Pop Tarts, Michael Musto and Albert Leave, 2200 Beaver Creek, 2900 Kershaw, 3600 Nancy, July 4, 1988 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0327)
  - August 14 & 15 1986 Provincetown, Boston, Michael Musto, Alice #6, August 14, 1986 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0328)
  - Rock & Roll Fag Bar at The World, House Tour, 1987 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0329)
    [1] -- Rock & Roll Fag Bar at The World, 9/22/1987 [2] -- House Tour, 10/24/1987
  - Nelson’s Hernia Operation, June 9, 1987 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0330)
  - Bad Tape, undated (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0331)
  - Christina, East Village, Carlo’s party, April 14, 1989 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0332)
  - A.A. Mix, undated (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0333)
  - Atlanta #10, Sophie’s Cabin, August 22, 1987 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0334)
  - Vito’s Boat Party #1, undated (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0335)
  - La Palace with RuPaul at Pyramid, January 30, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0336)
  - La Palace at Tunnel, January 22, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0337)
  - Fred as Rocco at The World, May 5, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0338)
  - John, Rhonda, Blackout and Me at Pier, Deee-Lite at The World, Sex Toys at Tunnel, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0339)
    [1] -- John, Rhonda, Blackout and Me at Pier, 5/28/1988 [2] -- Deee-Lite at The World, 6/3/1988 [3] -- Sex Toys at Tunnel, 6/3/1988
  - John Sex Bad Boys, John Sex at 5 Ninth watching himself on Japanese TV, Vito's Birthday, June 1986 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0340)
    [1] -- John Sex Bad Boys, 6/15/1986 [2] -- John Sex at 5 Ninth watching himself on Japanese TV, 6/17/1986 [3] -- Vito's Birthday, 6/18/1986
  - La Palace de Beaute (part 3), October 10, 1987 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0341)
  - Outlaw Party at Queensboro Bridge (taped by Lahoma), undated (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0342)
  - Woodstock IV (part 2), August 31, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0343)
  - Albert’s Fashions at Red Zone, April 1, 1989 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0344)
  - My Christmas Party at Tunnel, Alexis del Lago at The World, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0345)
    [1] -- My Christmas Party at Tunnel, 12/23/1987 [2] -- Alexis del Lago at The World, 1/3/1988
  - Brenda and Brandy at Limelight, Apollo Mystery Concert 2 (part 1), March 31, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0346)
  - Atlanta #7 - Playboy music video, August 20, 1987 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0347)
  - Celebrity Club with Albert, Michael Musto, Fashion Patrol, Christina, August 10, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0348)
  - New York to San Francisco #1, February 1986 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0349)
    [1] -- New York to San Francisco, 2/11/1986-2/13/1986
  - Bride Party, Vicki's Party, June 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0350)
    [1] -- Bride Party, 6/25/1988 [2] -- Vicki's Party, 6/26/1988
  - RuPaul Voyeur Party at Tunnel, undated (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0351)
  - Bunny Show at Pyramid (part 2), February 3, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0352)
  - Atlanta #5 Judy LaGrange Show, Provincetown, August 10, 1986 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0353)
  - Tabboo! & Alexis del Lago Pyramid, July 26, 1987 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0354)
  - Tunnel Benefit and After the Show, Samantha Fox Video Shoot in Front of 5 Ninth Avenue, April 4, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0355)
  - Leather Limelight, October 4, 1987 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0356)
  - Friday at 4-D, Albert at World Trade Center,Tunnel Sunday, Liz's Party, March 1987 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0357)
    [1] -- Friday at 4-D, 3/27/1987 [2] -- Albert at World Trade Center, 3/29/1987 [3] -- Tunnel Sunday, 3/29/1987 [4] -- Liz's Party
  - Atlanta #4, August 1987 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0358)
    [1] -- Atlanta #4, 8/16/1987-8/17/1987
  - Now Explosion at Pyramid, May 17, 1986 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0359)
  - Alice Bost, Zora at Green Street, November 3, 1987 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0360)
  - Shopping in Columbia, South Carolina, February 4, 1989 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0361)
  - Zette at The World, RuPaul to East Village, May 1986 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0362)
    [1] -- Zette at The World, 5/13/1986 [2] -- RuPaul to East Village, 5/22/1986
  - Susanne Bartsch at Copacabana, Weather Girls, October 29, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0363)
  - Porn 3, undated (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0364)
    [1] -- Porn 3, not a Nelson Sullivan tape
  - East Village Sunday, June 22, 1986 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0365)
  - Candy Store, November 15, 1986 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0366)
  - Liz’s Party, Avenue B and 6th Street, January 11, 1987 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0367)
  - Palladium #2 Downtown Party & Sister Dimension, May 28, 1986 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0368)
  - Zette at Pyramid, March 21, 1987 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0369)
  - May 17, 1987 (part 2) (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0370)
  - Gay Day 1986 Pyramid People (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0371)
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid (with Ethel Eichelberger, Tabboo!, Maize, Pet., Ger., etc.), Dean Johnson at Pyramid, 5 Ninth Avenue (with John Epperson to East Village), RuPaul at Jane West Hotel, June 8, 1986 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0372)
  - Katia Gallas, December 4, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0373)
  - Christina’s Apartment, Obsessions, November 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0374)
    [1] -- Christina’s Apartment, 11/11/1988 [2] -- Obsessions, 11/12/1988
  - Susanne Bartsch Copacabana Village People, August 25, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0375)
  - Eddie, Pop Tarts, Albert, Me in a Car, September 15, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0376)
  - Disco 88 and MTV, Michael Musto, The World, March 29, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0377)
  - Limelight Da DA, January 20, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0378)
  - Gay Day Night at Limelight, June 29, 1986 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0379)
  - Dale Livingston and Phil Mealy at the Montclair Art Museum, March 20, 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0380)
  - John Sex (with Wendy Wild and Chicklet) at Pyramid, Changing of the Guard (part 2), March 1988 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0381)
    [1] -- John Sex (with Wendy Wild and Chicklet) at Pyramid, 3/9/1988 [2] -- Changing of the Guard (part 2), 3/12/1988
  - My 40th Birthday at Pyramid, March 15, 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0382)
  - Downtown Dukes and Divas, November 15, 1987 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0383)
  - Tom’s Party, Lypsinka at La Mama, Albert & Musto, 1986 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0384)
    [1] -- Tom’s Party, 5/30/1986 [2] -- Lypsinka at La Mama, Albert & Musto, 6/3/1987
  - The Last Moments of 1986 - Eddie Braddock and Nelson Sullivan, December 31, 1986 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0385)
  - Trans Lux with Eddie and Nasomi, April 25, 1986 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0386)
  - Kennon Edit, undated (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0387)
  - Pyramid, Walk with Blackout, June 11, 1986 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0388)
  - My Provincetown, May 19, 1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0389)
  - Bunny & Lahoma (in blackface) at Fag Bar, Fashion Patrol at The World, December 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0390)
  - Dukes and Divas at New Music Seminar, Now Explosion at Limelight, undated (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0391)
  - Truck Ride to Bentley’s, DV8, Copacabana, September 7, 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0392)
    [1] -- Truck Ride to Bentley’s, 9/7/1988 [2] -- DV8, 12/29/1988 [3] -- Copacabana, 12/29/1988
  - Albert and Grandma, April 29, 1987 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0393)
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid with Dainty Adora, Keith Brazil, Christina, Tom Lohre Fixes Toilet, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0394)
    [1] -- WHISPERS at Pyramid with Dainty Adora, Keith Brazil, Christina, 9/14/1986 [2] -- Tom Lohre Fixes Toilet, 11/12/1988
  - Continuation of April 2 & 3, 1988, MK Straight to Hell Torso, April 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0395)
    [1] -- Continuation of April 2 & 3, 1988, 4/2/1988-4/3/1988 [2] -- MK Straight to Hell torso, 4/3/1988
  - Bunny (part 2), Tunnel, Rock and Roll Fag Bar at The World, Nazomi at Pyramid, February 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0396)
    [1] -- Bunny (part 2), 2/3/1988 [2] -- Tunnel, 2/12/1988 [3] -- Rock and Roll Fag Bar at The World, 2/16/1988 [4] -- Nazomi at Pyramid, 2/16/1988
  - Dainty, Albert’s Birthday, 1986 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0397)
    [1] -- Dainty, 1/19/1986 [2] -- Albert’s Birthday, 11/19/1986
  - Celebrity Club (part 2 of last tape), La Palace at The World, June 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0398)
    [1] -- Celebrity Club (part 2 of last tape), 6/22/1988 [2] -- La Palace at The World, 6/24/1988
  - Celebrity Club #2 Tunnel, April 19, 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0399)
  - Coney Island, Albert on the Street, June 21, 1986 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0400)
  - Celebrity Club, June 15, 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0401)
  - RuPaul (part 2), Rosser Atlanta, Snow at 5 Ninth Avenue, 1986-1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0402)
    [1] -- RuPaul (part 2), Rosser Atlanta, 12/11/1986 [2] -- Snow at 5 Ninth Avenue, 2/11/1989
  - Red Zone, Hollywood Twins, Copacabana Fabulous, April 27, 1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0403)
  - Church in Kershaw, Jeanie Brewer, February 2, 1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0404)
  - Celebrity Club at Tunnel, June 8, 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0405)
  - Arrive in Atlanta, On The American Music Show with Bandages Removed, RuPaul Arrives, February 1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0406)
    [1] -- Arrive in Atlanta, 2/6/1989 [2] -- On The American Music Show with Bandages Removed, 2/7/1989 [3] -- RuPaul Arrives, 2/8/1989
  - King and Queen of Downtown, TV, Dainty, Next day - King & Queen of Downtown on TV, Dainty, John Kelly, undated (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0407)
  - Atlanta: RuPaul at Colorbox (part 1), Thrift Store Shopping with Tom Zarrilli, February 10, 1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0408)
  - McDonald’s Outlaw Party for Frank Roccio (with Michael Alig), Floyd’s Party, March 18, 1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0409)